[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[Abyss]
Captain Xin.
Xiaoliang is here.
Come here.
Well...
I'll leave you two alone.
I'll get going.
What is it now?
Mom asked me to bring you
some late-night snacks.
She said she couldn't reach you
on the phone.
Just leave it there.
Go home early if there's nothing else.
I'm busy right now.
[3/12 Case]
[Li Fang]
[Liu Xiaohua]
[3/12 Case]
[Du Juan]
Dad.
Look at these cases.
Once these people are caught,
are they as good as dead?
The law will judge them.
My job
is to catch them
and bring them before the court.
So, if a person—
a good person,
to help a friend,
accidentally did something wrong,
can he still be spared?
That depends on
whether it's a public security case
or a criminal case.
It's not really a case.
Maybe he just lost his head for a moment
and had no choice.
What do you mean by having no choice?
Under the law,
there is no such thing
as having no choice.
Making a mistake while helping a friend—
that's not a friend.
That's an accomplice.
You don't have to yell. I can hear you.
I left the food here.
Remember to eat it.
I'm leaving now.
[Huangshui Public Security Bureau]
[Episode 5]
[Emergency]
[Huangshui County, 8 years ago, 2004]
Boss, you're finally here.
Boss, my wife is on the night shift today.
The kid is home alone.
I've been feeling uneasy about it.
-So I…
-Alright, alright!
I know you're worried about
your little one.
Go back now.
W-Well then, thank you.
Thanks.
Captain Xin.
What's the situation now?
The victim's name is Chen Chunli.
Female, 37 years old.
No fixed occupation.
She's been selling fruit
at a stall for the past few months.
She was stabbed 3 times in the abdomen.
Multiple abrasions all over her body.
She crawled onto the highway,
was found by a truck driver,
and was sent to the hospital.
She lost a lot of blood
and is still being resuscitated.
Where is the driver?
At their station.
Ready to be transferred at any time.
Oh, right.
The emergency doctor
specifically mentioned
that the wounds are very unusual,
approximately triangular.
This is the 5th case.
If I can't catch them,
I've lived my life in vain.
Have the victim's family been notified?
Yes, they have.
They are on their way.
Xin.
I know you're busy.
I'm not rushing you.
It's just that...
Xiaoliang hasn't come back.
I've looked for him.
And I've called all his teachers.
I'm just worried.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid he got into trouble outside
and was taken to the police station again.
Can you ask your colleagues
if anyone has seen him tonight?
I'm too ashamed to ask.
What does that mean?
Is he only my son?
Does he have nothing to do with you?
Are you going to do something?
Look at the time!
Aren't you going to do something?
You find...
You're back?
Come on. Where have you been?
Xin Xiaoliang!
[Emergency]
I closed the stall late
last night,
so I missed the last bus.
Of course I wouldn't splurge on a cab.
So I figured I'd just
walk back along that road.
That road was quite remote,
but usually there are cars passing by.
Unexpectedly,
as I was walking...
H-Help!
Kill her!
I passed out
from the pain.
They probably thought I was dead.
First, they took my bag.
Then my wallet.
And the gold ring
I always wore on this hand.
Then they
walked away cursing.
I didn't dare to move.
And it took me a long time
to get over the pain.
When it got quiet,
I finally dared
to crawl toward...
toward the road
where I could see cars.
Are you sure there were three of them?
Yes.
Did you get a clear look at their faces?
No.
It was too dark.
They all seemed to be wearing masks.
What about their voices?
Anything special about their voices?
Local accents or from out of town?
I didn't catch any accents.
But...
the one I-I hit
seemed a bit younger.
The other two were older.
One young, two older?
Can you be more specific?
The young one was in his early 20s.
The older two
were in their 40s or 50s.
Weren't you with your son?
Where is he?
My son
failed the college entrance exam 3 times.
I just sent him out of town a few days ago
to study at my brother's place.
But officer,
I don't want my son to know about this.
So...
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
I-I'll go call the doctor.
No, no need.
Officer,
I'm sorry
I couldn't be of more help.
But I really can't take it anymore.
One last question.
The knife that stabbed you...
Come on. That's enough.
She's in so much pain.
If y-you guys
have any other questions,
c-can't you come back a few days later?
Let her get some good rest.
O-Okay?
How can we catch the suspects
without asking her questions?
Alright, focus on recovering for now.
We'll come back in a while.
[Operating Room]
[Room 03]
Zhao.
Captain Xin.
Chen Chunli gave birth to Guo Pengfei
when she was 17.
Guo Pengfei's biological father
was about the same age as her.
He couldn't take responsibility.
He and his family moved to Fujian
over a decade ago,
and he hasn't come back since.
Her current boyfriend is Chen Dingkun,
a teacher
at No. 3 Middle School of the county.
He's divorced.
They started dating half a year ago
and moved in together
two and a half months ago.
They reportedly have a good relationship.
He was on duty at school
during the incident,
so he can be ruled out.
Guo Pengfei failed
the college entrance exam
and is retaking it.
A few days before the incident,
Chen Chunli sent him
to study at her cousin's place in Qidu.
What about Chen Chunli's parents?
They died when she was very young.
Chen Chunli grew up at her aunt's house
until she got pregnant out of wedlock.
Her aunt thought she was a disgrace,
kicked her out,
and they never contacted each other again.
She was just a teenager.
How did she raise her son alone?
Working odd jobs.
Just from the jobs we investigated,
she's done 7 or 8 different ones.
This area here.
And here.
How many pieces so far?
Including your three,
36.
Let's test the primary crime scene first
when we get back.
The blood by the road
should be the victim's.
Surviving this much blood loss,
she's really tough.
Any other findings?
We also found this at the scene.
[Changle Condoms]
A condom wrapper?
A major breakthrough.
This is the first time we've found this
at a crime scene.
Right.
Changle brand?
[Changle Condoms]
This brand of condoms
isn't sold on the market.
It's distributed for free
by the Family Planning Commission
to the family planning offices
of various units.
There are a lot of them,
and they have no special marks,
so they're hard to trace.
Let's see if we can find
any biological traces first.
Okay.
We found a used
[Changle Condoms]
Changle condom wrapper at the scene.
[No biological traces were recovered.]
However,
we didn't extract
any useful biological traces.
[The People's Police Serve the People]
We also tested
36 blood samples.
[Crime Scene Evidence]
After ruling out Chen Chunli's blood,
[Victim's Blood Type: O]
[Blood Test Result: AB]
we found a stone
with AB-type blood on it.
This stone is most likely
the one Chen Chunli said
she used to fight back.
We used the DNA from the blood
and the skin flakes under the nails
of Liu Xiaohua,
the victim in the 3rd group
of the 3/12 Case,
to make a comparison.
They...
didn't match.
Since multiple clues
point to a three-person gang,
I think we have
the DNA of two of them.
[Crime Scene Evidence]
You've already concluded
that Chen Chunli's case and the 3/12 Case
were committed
by the same group of suspects?
Yes.
I don't think
we can rule out
the possibility of a copycat crime.
The possibility of a copycat crime exists,
but it's very small.
[Crime Scene Evidence]
There are 3 reasons.
First,
Huangshui has low population mobility.
Second, the criminals' psychology.
Third, the similarities
in the murder weapons.
Now, let's assign tasks.
Fanjie and Wang, you each take a team,
work with the traffic police,
and check
all the major routes out of town,
highway exits, bus stations,
and train stations.
Zhao Ganzhe and I will coordinate
with the local police stations
to check hospitals,
clinics, pharmacies, and hotels.
Judging from the amount of blood
on the stone,
the suspect must have
a large wound on his forehead.
He definitely needs to get it treated.
Let's try to catch him
within 24 hours.
Yes!
Go to the First Hospital first.
I'll contact the police stations.
I can do that
by myself.
You were working overtime
before Chen Chunli's incident.
Up to now,
you've been working for 40 hours straight
without rest.
You should go home and sleep, you know?
The guys are all working.
You want the captain to go home?
You're human,
not Superman.
If you drop dead from exhaustion,
I can't take the responsibility!
You're a detective.
Why are you afraid of everything?
Yes, I'm naturally timid.
Anyway, if you don't go back to rest,
I'll report it to the bureau leaders
and see what they say.
Why don't you report it to the head
of the Public Security Department?
I don't have their phone number.
I'll kick...
Besides,
even if it's not for yourself,
at least do it for your child.
Yesterday,
your wife couldn't find Xiaoliang,
and she even called me.
You can't always be busy with work.
You have to spend time with your child.
Alright, alright.
Don't mention him.
He's no different from a punk.
I have to bail him out
of the police station all the time.
His father is a cop.
I can't afford to lose face like this.
He's just a kid.
That's how teenagers are.
When you were his age,
you were much more annoying than him.
I'm taking the car.
You can take a taxi.
Call me if you need anything.
Not bad. You can even pull off combos.
Come on.
Come out!
Damn.
You can even pull off combos.
Why didn't you go to school?
Come out!
Come out.
You scared me.
Why didn't you go to school?
I asked for leave.
Mom agreed before she went to work.
What are you doing?
How did you get this?
I fell while playing basketball.
When did it happen?
Yesterday.
Don't pretend to care about me.
You never ask about me.
Yesterday?
The one I-I hit
seemed a bit younger.
He was in his early 20s.
It hurts!
What are you doing?
Does this look like a fall?
Tell me,
how did this happen?
I was beaten up!
By whom? Where?
With what?
At the basketball court!
We got into a fight over the court!
Some guy I didn't know hit me
with a brick!
Tell me the truth!
I am telling the truth!
Xin Jiran, I'm your son!
I'm not a criminal!
Why are you yelling at me?
What's your blood type?
What's my blood type?
You're my dad!
You don't know my blood type?
I'm asking you!
I don't know!
Go ask Mom!
Xin Xiaoliang.
Where are the things inside?
[Changle Condoms]
What things?
Why are a few missing?
Did you take them?
You should ask yourself.
Did you forget to restock
after using them?
I'm asking you!
[Changle Condoms]
Where are they?
Yes, I used them.
I blew them up like balloons.
I even put one on the door handle
downstairs.
Didn't you see it?
What?
Are you running low?
I'll go buy more for you, alright?
Or just don't buy them.
Give me a little brother or sister.
Anyway, one more or one less kid
in this family...
Xin Jiran!
Xin Xiaoliang.
Before I come back,
don't you dare step out of this door.
Try me!
We'll see about that!
I'm going out!
Let go of me!
Let... Let go of me!
Let go!
Let go of me, Xin Jiran!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
Dad, don't handcuff me!
Dad!
Dad, I'm your son!
I... I'm not a criminal!
Why did you handcuff me?
Xin Jiran!
I'm going to call my mom
and tell her to divorce you,
so you'll be single
for the rest of your life!
You handcuffed me? I'm your son!
Luo.
Here.
Why isn't it in a bag?
Don't ask so many questions.
Do it as fast as you can.
I'll wait in the hallway.
Okay.
[Devoted to Duty, Clean and Upright]
I have a folding bed in my office.
Go in and get some sleep.
No need.
I'll just wait here for the results.
The results are already out.
So fast?
You don't need a DNA test for this.
Even the blood types don't match.
Why do you look like
you're relieved?
Where did you get that gauze anyway?
Don't ask if you see me as your brother.
I'm leaving.
I'll treat you to a meal some other day.
Xin, take it easy!
[Old-Fashioned
Fried Cakes and Sesame Balls]
Well, I'll give you a bag.
Choose for yourself, kid.
Xin Xiaoliang.
Xin Jiran made a mistake.
I apologize to you.
Xiaoliang!
Xiaoliang?
Xiaoliang, open your mouth.
Come on, open your mouth.
Open your mouth!
Hello?
Room 201, Unit 6, Building 6,
Jinhua Beili.
A boy, 18 years old!
It might be an asthma attack.
He's not breathing!
He's not breathing.
Hurry, hurry!
Please, hurry!
[In Memoriam]
[A Young Soul Leaves This World,
While Loving Hearts Weep Forever]
Sorry, time's up.
If you miss the time,
you'll have to wait in line again.
[In Memoriam]
[A Young Soul Leaves This World,
While Loving Hearts Weep Forever]
[In Memoriam]
[A Young Soul Leaves This World,
While Loving Hearts Weep Forever]
[In Memoriam]
[Serve the People]
I am guilty.
I'm turning myself in.
I spent 6 years in prison.
For the past 6 years,
I've been thinking about one question—
what's the meaning of my life?
Why don't I just die?
There is only one answer—
if the 3/12 Case is not solved,
I won't be able to rest in peace.
You asked me
why I didn't go to the police station
to explain.
I'm not even afraid of death.
Why would I be afraid
of being misunderstood?
Some things
are as important as life.
What things?
Ideals?
Faith?
Reputation?
I have none of those.
I am a reckless man who caused
his whole family's deaths.
I even feel that
if I die on the street tomorrow,
no one will shed a tear for me.
You're wrong.
You used to be a good cop.
The people you helped
will remember you.
Fresh graduates
are just naive.
I don't think so.
I graduated from the police academy
20 years ago
I agree with Li Cheng.
So,
you must not be here to arrest me.
You old bastard.
You're pretty quick.
What's the point of talking back to me?
Let's go. Come back with me.
Explain the situation clearly.
Don't complicate the case.
Wait. Can you guarantee
I'll be out in 24 hours?
I can't.
But I can tell you
the latest news.
The 3/12 Case has been reopened.
Our chance has come.
Officially reopened?
Not yet.
It'll happen in a day or two.
Did you find clues
on Song Laifu?
Chief Tu.
The DNA comparison results confirm
that before his death, Song Laifu
had a direct conflict
with one of the suspects at large
in the 3/12 Case.
This indicates that the two cases
are highly related.
I suggest reopening the 3/12 Case
and investigating the two cases together.
I personally agree.
First thing tomorrow morning,
I will report to Chief Qi in person.
Alright, Chief Tu.
Then I'll continue to investigate
Song Laifu's movements before his death.
Xin Jiran—
have you found him?
Not yet.
Since the blood on Song Laifu's stick
wasn't Xin Jiran's,
does that make him less of a suspect?
Chief Tu,
before Song Laifu died,
he had a conflict with a suspect
in the 3/12 Case.
This doesn't contradict the possibility
that Xin Jiran
killed Song Laifu.
Based on the evidence,
I think
Xin Jiran is still the prime suspect.
The blood on Song Laifu's stick
belongs to one of the three murderers?
As soon as Luo Jinsong got the results,
he messaged me,
hoping I'd bring you back to the station
to prove your innocence.
Someone as cautious as him
broke the rules for you.
And you said you'd die on the street
with no one caring?
What do you take
us old guys for?
I'm telling you,
even Fanjie,
who may chew you out,
might still want to help you deep down.
What you guys think doesn't matter.
I just want to solve the case now.
Of the two suspects at large,
could Song Laifu be
the one without a DNA record?
Could he and Bi Dehua
both have been silenced
by the third person?
Alright, alright, alright.
Come back with me,
prove your innocence,
and continue investigating
after you're out.
Come on.
No need to take out the handcuffs, right?
I don't even ha—
You old bastard.
It's okay if you don't trust Fanjie,
but you don't trust me either?
Where's the car?
Right at the door.
Stop!
Old bastard, stop right there!
You went back on your word!
Stop!
Come on!
Old Foodie!
Old...
Old Foodie, you don't
have much stamina!
Old bastard.
If you want to run, then run.
Why did you stop to mock me?
You can outrun me.
Can you outrun Li Cheng?
Li Cheng, hold him down!
He's on my side!
I'm not an official police officer yet.
I have no law enforcement powers.
I can't hold him down.
You brat.
Now you are following the rules, huh?
Zhao!
The three of us—
with you in the light, me in the dark,
and Li Cheng in the middle—
we make a pretty good team.
I'm not afraid to tell you
that I plan to go to Xidu
and verify once again
whether Song Laifu
ever returned to Huangshui
while he was working there 8 years ago,
and whether he had time
to commit the crime.
For an inter-provincial investigation
into a case
from so many years ago,
you know how long it takes
through official channels.
Leave it to me,
and it'll be much faster!
Don't think
just because the blood on the stick
isn't yours,
Fanjie will give up looking for you!
Then let him.
Li Cheng.
Let's keep in touch.
Bro.
I'm sorry.
Should we keep chasing him?
Why did Song Laifu come here?
Maybe he was meeting someone?
Or maybe he hid something here.
Didn't you say
you saw a photo
with about half of it torn off
at Han Pinmu's place?
Does the background match this part?